{
	"questions": [
		{
			"correctAnswer": "True",
			"question": "Dynamic modeling involves determining how objects interact with each other to support a use case.",
			"answers": [
			  "True",
			  "False"
			]
		},
		{
			"correctAnswer": "False",
			"question": "State-dependent dynamic modeling is not important for real-time design.",
			"answers": [
			  "True",
			  "False"
			]
		},
		{
			"correctAnswer": "True",
			"question": "Communication diagrams show objects as boxes and their message interactions as arrows.",
			"answers": [
			  "True",
			  "False"
			]
		},
		{
			"correctAnswer": "False",
			"question": "Sequence diagrams do not emphasize the messages passed between objects.",
			"answers": [
			  "True",
			  "False"
			]
		},
		{
			"correctAnswer": "True",
			"question": "In stateless dynamic modeling, the first step is to start with a use case.",
			"answers": [
			  "True",
			  "False"
			]
		},
		{
			"correctAnswer": "Card Reader Interface",
			"question": "Which of the following is a boundary object in the Validate PIN use case?",
			"answers": [
			  "ATM Transaction",
			  "Debit Card",
			  "Card Reader Interface",
			  "PIN Validation Transaction Manager"
			]
		},
		{
			"correctAnswer": "Message Sequence Description",
			"question": "What describes the sequence of object interactions corresponding to communication or sequence diagrams?",
			"answers": [
			  "Statechart",
			  "Message Sequence Description",
			  "Use Case Diagram",
			  "Class Diagram"
			]
		},
		{
			"correctAnswer": "Alarm Service",
			"question": "In the 'View Alarms' use case, which object responds with information about the requested alarm?",
			"answers": [
			  "Operator Interaction",
			  "Alarm Service",
			  "Boundary Object",
			  "Control Object"
			]
		},
		{
			"correctAnswer": "Withdraw Funds",
			"question": "Which use case involves the Cash Dispenser Interface as a boundary object?",
			"answers": [
			  "Validate PIN",
			  "View Alarms",
			  "Withdraw Funds",
			  "Make Order Request"
			]
		},
		{
			"correctAnswer": "Statecharts",
			"question": "State-dependent control objects are modeled using what?",
			"answers": [
			  "Sequence Diagrams",
			  "Statecharts",
			  "Communication Diagrams",
			  "Use Case Descriptions"
			]
		}
	]
}
